SPEAKER_01: Can I ask you a question? Of course you can.
SPEAKER_01: Can you get me out of this?
SPEAKER_01: place.
SPEAKER_01: I'm afraid I'm of no use to you there.
SPEAKER_01: Why couldn't they put me in a proper...
SPEAKER_01: prison a better facility.
SPEAKER_01: He wasn't available. You're putting me in a muddle!
SPEAKER_01: It's a secure training.
SPEAKER_01: Training.
SPEAKER_01: What, have you trained enough?
SPEAKER_01: I was four.
SPEAKER_01: The other boys just scream all the time.
SPEAKER_01: And you've got problems.
SPEAKER_01: forwards in the shower
SPEAKER_01: Young and free.
SPEAKER_01: All the way from Korea.
SPEAKER_01: every time you see Steve McDonald.
SPEAKER_01: I don't understand.
SPEAKER_01: What's the best place for you to be?
SPEAKER_01: Stay at home until his trial.
SPEAKER_01: accused of such a serious crime.
SPEAKER_00: All the way from Corrie.
SPEAKER_01: It's all accused.
SPEAKER_01: If I did it, if I...
SPEAKER_01: And then again, he got...
SPEAKER_01: I didn't so...
SPEAKER_01: and this wasn't my decision.
SPEAKER_01: I'mma get in there.
SPEAKER_01: Nothing has been destroyed.
SPEAKER_01: Get you know where it's gonna be
SPEAKER_01: I'm an Osama local.
SPEAKER_01: We need to sit down.
SPEAKER_01: Jamie, if you don't...
SPEAKER_01: I don't mean you don't know you
SPEAKER_01: Does that mean you don't know each other?
SPEAKER_01: Nothing's been decided yet.
SPEAKER_01: You need to sit.
SPEAKER_01: I don't want to sit down.
SPEAKER_01: Don't sit down, I have to...
SPEAKER_01: Stop this discussion.
SPEAKER_01: Do you?
SPEAKER_01: It pisses you off, doesn't it?
SPEAKER_01: That's a woman
SPEAKER_01: Jamie, if you don't...
SPEAKER_01: Do not sit. Luna!
SPEAKER_00: I'mma get in there for the trial.
SPEAKER_00: You know where it's gonna be? London or Saint Malo?
SPEAKER_00: Don't!
SPEAKER_00: No! You're not!
SPEAKER_00: Tell me when to sit down!
SPEAKER_00: You do not!
SPEAKER_00: Control Y!
SPEAKER_00: Look at me now!
SPEAKER_00: YOU KNO-
SPEAKER_01: You cannot control what I do in my life! Get that in the fucking little head of yours!
SPEAKER_01: Fucking hell!